export const questions = [
    {
        question: "What HTML tag makes a link?",
        wrongAnswers: ["<tr>", "<img />", "<br />"],
        correctAnswer: "<a>"
    },
    {
        question: "What HTML tag makes a new line?",
        wrongAnswers: ["<tr>", "<img />", "<a>"],
        correctAnswer: "<br />"
    },
    {
        question: "What HTML tag do you put things in if you want them to appear on the page?",
        wrongAnswers: ["<html>", "<head>", "<p>"],
        correctAnswer: "<body>"
    },
    {
        question: "What tag attribute can you put CSS code into?",
        wrongAnswers: ["title", "height", "width"],
        correctAnswer: "style"
    },
    {
        question: "What tag do you use to put a title on a table?",
        wrongAnswers: ["<tr>", "<title>", "<th>"],
        correctAnswer: "<caption>"
    },
    {
        question: "What CSS property makes the colour of the page change?",
        wrongAnswers: ["font-color", "font-size", "color"],
        correctAnswer: "background-color"
    },
    {
        question: "Give an example of a boolean attribute.",
        wrongAnswers: ["height", "style", "title"],
        correctAnswer: "autoplay"
    },
    {
        question: "What is wrong with the code <body>Hello<body/>?",
        wrongAnswers: ["it should be </body>Hello<body>", "it should be </body>Hello</body>", "it should be <body>Hello<body>"],
        correctAnswer: "it should be <body>Hello</body>"
    },
    {
        question: "What CSS property makes text go bold?",
        wrongAnswers: ["font-size", "text-decoration", "bold"],
        correctAnswer: "font-weight"
    },
    {
        question: "What attribute of the img tag displays things on the page if the picture cannot be?",
        wrongAnswers: ["src", "height", "style"],
        correctAnswer: "alt"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of file ends in a three letter code of .mp4?",
        wrongAnswers: ["sound", "picture", "HTML"],
        correctAnswer: "video"
    },
    {
        question: "What tag adds comments to your HTML code?",
        wrongAnswers: ["<title>", "<caption>", "<comment>"],
        correctAnswer: "<!-->"
    },
    {
        question: "What two other tags do li tags need to work?",
        wrongAnswers: ["<ul> or <h1>", "<h1> or <ol>", "<h1> or <p>"],
        correctAnswer: "<ul> or <ol>"
    },
    {
        question: "What is an example of a CSS event?",
        wrongAnswers: ["start", "stop", "play"],
        correctAnswer: "hover"
    },
    {
        question: "What should every CSS declaration end with?",
        wrongAnswers: ["=", "a closing tag", ":"],
        correctAnswer: ";"
    },
    {
        question: "What is CSS code called if it starts with a ., e.g. .glow?",
        wrongAnswers: ["inline", "external", "value"],
        correctAnswer: "class"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a CSS inline style?",
        wrongAnswers: ["CSS code in a style tag", "CSS code in an external css file", "HTML code"],
        correctAnswer: "CSS code in a style attribute"
    },
    {
        question: "What CSS code is an example of a function?",
        wrongAnswers: ["text-shadow", "background-image", "a:hover"],
        correctAnswer: "radial-gradient"
    },
    {
        question: "Which part of this CSS code is called the selector by experts? tr { color:red; }",
        wrongAnswers: ["color", "red", "all of the code"],
        correctAnswer: "tr"
    },
    {
        question: "What is wrong with the code <br>?",
        wrongAnswers: ["nothing", "it should be </br>", `it should be <br\\>`],
        correctAnswer: "it should be <br />"
    }
]